Good morning!
- Nanaka, no makeup?
- I overslept.
Online till late?
I bet she was playing games again.
Mai! We're here.
Cute! Can I borrow it?
Hang on!
We don't have time.
Oh...
Mai and Risa,
you need to wake Nanaka earlier.
Yes. It's their fault.
- I tried to wake you up.
- You brute! Help me Mai Mai!
Mai...
She's not listening.
Yes.
Ten minute call.
In-ear monitor checked?
The boss is coming today!
Get ready!
- Risa, can you take the mic after me?
- Okay.
This is the last gig of the tour!
Girls are you ready?
Let's give the fans
the gig of the century!
Huddle!
Happy Fanfare!
Let's go!
- Let's do this!
- I'm so tense!
Himena
Risa
Nanaka
Minami
Mai
Just for a second
Don't look away, please
In one instant
I'll take you prisoner
In the depths of my heart
I heard the vibration
Are you ready? Why don't you ask me?
It's already begun...
This pinkie promise
I'm always looking for the lies
In your shifting, lonely gaze
But I can't lie to you
The dream that lights my way
Is only meant for you
No matter how far you
I'll keep you to myself
Just for a second
Don't look away, please
You're my only number one
Why are you waiting?
It's a one second love story
It's so simple, this love
In one instant
I'll take you prisoner
Thanks for coming to
so many gigs this year.
How was it, Nanaka?
I'm nervous...
Thanks for supporting
our 4th year tour.
And making beautiful memories
with us.
Thank you!
And please go on supporting all five
of us in our 5th year.
October 27th 2024
Happy Fanfare
Congratulations on
IDOL EXPO TOKYO 2024
Happy Fanfare will be at the IDOL EXPO
TOKYO 2024 again this year!
And...
we're the closing act
on the main stage!
Congratulations!
Thank you! Same pose as usual.
I remember you, Mr.Suzuki.
Thank you.
Thank you Mr.Yama.
- Congratulations!
- Thanks.
- Is that a new top?
- You noticed.
Of course. It's really cute.
You said you liked guys in hoodies.
Did I say that?
Three photos. Okay?
Nanaka's popular.
Her game commentary went viral.
Have we got the line-up
for the new single?
Not yet.
Love you.
You danced so well today.
You really inspired me to work harder.
What does that mean?
I bought 50 CD's for this event.
Wow, thank you!
You didn't have to do that.
We'll make you the top idol for sure.
Thank you.
I am going to work for this.
- Till the next gig.
- I love you.
Thank you.
- Bye.
- Thank you. Bye bye!
Thanks for everything.
Nice to see you.
Okay girls, we're here.
- Doesn't your mum cook?
- She does.
Listen, guys...
The boss was laughing but he meant it.
You're still not there yet.
Your dancing is a mess.
The festival will be a disaster.
- But, Saya...
- No "Buts!"
We have so many fan events
we don't have time to practice.
That's no excuse.
You're not as busy as the top groups.
Okay.
And the dorm girls are always late.
I'm sorry.
No staying up late. No alcohol.
SNS till 24:00. And stream for the fans.
All of you.
Got it!
See you tomorrow.
Get some rest.
Thank you.
Oh, hi Yuya.
Thanks for coming today.
I saw you, really.
I'm not lying.
I sent you a sign
but you didn't notice.
I'm a bit bored with Happy Fanfare these days.
Why is Mai always in the center?
Don't tease me.
It was so cute.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Forget about it. Who cares?
But they're right. I'ｍ not ready.
We're all in the same boat.
Here.
Hey, are you free next Tuesday?
We're off that day.
What?
Wouldn't you like to see an elephant
or a giraffe?
What?
Let's go to the Zoo.
Why?
I'm going with a friend.
Let's all go together.
Just go with your friend.
Well, it's just that...
Oh, you mean Yuya?
Yes...
I get it now.
Please. It's his birthday,
I can't go on a date with him alone.
Invite some other friends.
- You want decoys?
- No, more like bodyguards.
Okay, but why the Zoo?
Because it isn't crowded. People will
be busy looking at the animals.
Please!
- Monkeys!
- Really?
Look at them.
Cute. Looks like it's trying to hide.
Are they a family?
They're eating something.
Thank you!
It flew off.
Thank you.
Um, how did you do that?
That's a secret, Mai Yamaoka.
A second of Zero Gravity
Reach out your hands
A second with you is real
It's fate that we're in love
No matter how far I go
I'll take you along
In a split second, look at me
Just dance, we are so free
Meaning is meaningless
Are you going to hesitate?
This split second love story
It's just love you know
In a split second
I'll take you prisoner
Wow! Great!
The real thing!
I had no idea you wanted to be an idol.
- You would just have laughed at me.
- I totally get it.
That's why you did Karaoke?
- Of course.
- Karaoke?
I practiced at a Karaoke place.
Kei used to work there.
Karaoke wasn't allowed at our school.
Delinquents!
Nobody ever knew.
It's so cool. Your dream came true.
Yeah, but I'm not there yet.
We want to play Tokyo Dome.
Wow!
What was Mai like when she was
in junior high?
Serious. A closed book.
- Still the same.
- And she's always worrying.
- You're the same!
- Me?
Sorry, sorry, it's my turn.
- I love this one.
- What? Really?
Thanks. Can I sing it?
Christmas Eve and I'm all dolled up
In my favorite dress
Your text says you're sorry
Panic at the crossroads
You're always late when it matters
Makes me cry and cry ah-ha
So cold these blues
White Christmas tonight
A snowflake logo on the screen
I still don't quite believe
I'm in Tokyo.
Where are you from?
From the boonies in Shizuoka.
I know. It feels unreal.
You're a city girl. Hiroshima, right?
They even have an acting school there.
Yes, but...
In the real countryside nobody studies
and everyone spies on everyone else.
Same everywhere.
Can you see that thing
in your hometown?
That...
What?
The sun thing.
I mean...
That sunrise...
Are you drunk?
The snowman sunrise...
What's that?
My house is near the Pacific.
The rising sun reflects
on the dark sea.
It looks like it's a head and a body,
like a red snowman.
It's overlapping, refraction,
or something.
It's really beautiful.
- Wow! I'd love to see that.
- Yeah, me too.
Not for you. Tokyo Tower's
enough for you Hiroshima guys.
Are you leaving?
Toilet.
Me too.
They're dating, right?
- Nanaka and Yuya?
- Yes.
They met online.
Yuya is an online gamer.
Cool, isn't it?
He's got way more followers than us.
Is that allowed?
I hear it's tough for idols
with all the rules.
About dating and stuff?
Yeah of course that's true.
She's so happy. I can't stop her.
Promise you won't tell anyone.
Of course.
I didn't rat on you in school.
You weren't allowed to be working
there either.
I was saving. It was my uncle's place.
I earned enough to go to the UK
for three years.
I went to mime school.
You're so confident, Kei...
You mean I'm arrogant.
I didn't mean that.
Sorry. I've been feeling
a bit down recently.
I can't sing or dance, but everyone
cheers when I go on stage.
I feel like a fraud.
It's normal.
I met this old juggler in the UK.
He said if you wait to be perfect...
you'll die practicing.
That's probably true.
Show me something.
Like what?
One of your tricks.
- Anything?
- Yes, you choose.
For free?
I'll show you something special.
Just like Spider-Man.
Never seen it.
How did you do that?
It's a secret.
Happy Fanfare's new single:
The Colour of Your Tears
Okay, here's the line-up
for the new single.
The line-up is...
Center this time, number 1 is...
Nanaka.
Okay.
Nanaka
Mai is 2.
Minami is 3.
Risa 4.
Himena 5.
Nanaka. It's your first time,
but don't be nervous.
Okazaki, can you take over?
Thank you!
Go through the moves.
Please.
Let's start with a warm up.
- I made a pile today.
- Really?
Because I look them in the eyes.
Wow, it's like your home.
It is my home. I live in here.
- Really?
- Yep.
You sleep here?
See, like this.
I was on the road last year.
It's a waste of money to pay rent.
Wow. I can't imagine.
Isn't it tough?
Well, it's easy to find toilets.
I use the public baths. It's not so bad.
- Do you choose everything?
- Of course.
You're amazing.
It's normal.
We have producers, you know.
Oh...
They decide the songs,
lyrics and everything.
Do they decide the lead singer?
They usually put the most popular one
in the center.
We're pros so we have to work
with any material.
That's what they tell us.
Want a ride?
It's late. It's up to you.
I'll give you some.
- Really?
- I've got lots.
Thanks.
If you can do it
I'll teach you another trick.
I'll try.
- Six times in a row.
- Seriously?
Yes.
- Next month we're in a festival.
- A music festival?
There'll be lots of idol groups.
Happy Fanfare are on last.
Headlining? That's amazing.
- You should come.
- Yeah, I wouldn't miss it.
- It's not your thing...
- It is.
Oh no.
What?
I'm alone in a boy's house.
Yeah, so?
The sheriff's going to kill me.
Who's the sheriff?
Minami is stricter than Risa.
Will she kill me too?
I bet you always take girls for a ride.
I don't do it all the time.
Just sometimes.
I'll give you this in return.
Thanks Kei.
Mai...
Do you hold the fans' hands like this?
No. This is different.
It's not the usual handshake.
Risa
Did you see this, Mai?
What is she doing?
It's right before the festival!
Is this guy Nanaka's boyfriend?
Isn't he a Happy Fanfare geek?
Who is Nanaka?
- Happy Fanfare?
- Butt out you lot!
- Nanaka and that guy!!
- It stinks!
- She's dating a fan!
- So lame.
Yuya, don't sweat it.
Give us Nanaka back.
Leave poor Nanaka alone.
If I was a Youtuber
could I go out with her?
It's a shitstorm!
He's dating an idol?
If you don't talk we can't help you.
At your audition you said
you'd dreamed
of being an idol since you were
a child.
You wanted to be the best.
We want your dream to come true.
We really do.
And so do your fans, of course.
And your parents.
That's why we're putting in the work.
But now your fans
feel you betrayed them.
Do you understand?
Yes.
So, what do you want to do
about this?
These photos...
were leaked from
Nanaka's private SNS.
Private account? Did you know?
She had a private account
for her friends...
She said she's sorry
she was so stupid.
We'll have to think about her future.
Please don't speak to anyone.
You know we're here to protect
and nurture you.
But if you do selfish stuff like this,
we can't help.
Think of all the grown-ups who are
working for you.
This isn't a game.
Please understand that.
Will we still be able to play
the festival?
I haven't heard.
I'll let you know as soon as possible.
That's it for today.
Hello.
I'm sorry about this.
It was my fault. I'm sorry.
Anyone else?
I'm risking everything here.
I trust you guys.
I won't forgive you
if any of you betray me again.
I won't forgive you.
Nanaka said they would break up.
I heard from Yuya.
Is there no other way?
Rules are rules.
She either quits or they break up.
It's too bad because they love
each other.
There's no other way.
Should I stop seeing you too?
It's still crazy, isn't it?
Today I'm online because
I need to tell you something.
Most of you probably know that
someone uploaded
private photos of me on social media.
A lot of what people wrote about me
just isn't true.
I'm just good friends with Yuya,
the Youtuber.
I'm sorry about my stupid actions.
I know you've always supported me,
and I've caused problems for everyone.
For all the trouble I've caused...
I'm truly sorry.
I'll do my best to be the girl
that you want to believe in.
That's all for today.
Finished?
Yes. Everyone was nice.
Nanaka...
I've got to pack my things.
Are you really going?
They already told my parents
I can commute from my home.
That's going to be hard.
I'll talk to Saya.
It's not so far. Anyway,
the agency talked to my parents.
Well, maybe, but...
If you need anything...
You could buy me a juice.
I'm thirsty from all that talking.
There you go.
One more thing...
What?
Can you delete Yuya for me?
You don't have to do that.
Please. I'll definitely
get in touch with him.
But I can't do it myself.
Please.
I don't want to do it.
You have to do that yourself.
Mai, please...
I don't want to give up being an idol.
Do you want to delete Yuya?
Yuya has been deleted.
Sorry for showing up.
I wanted to talk to you.
I'm sorry.
Listen!
You owe him an explanation.
Yuya.
I'm sorry.
But if you care about Nanaka,
please leave her alone.
Yuya...
This is crazy!
You don't need to follow their
stupid rules! You're an adult!
The love clock is ticking loud...
Center: Mai
I'll remove the batteries
From my tick-tock heart
Happy love is clouding over now
Blowing out the candles I wished on
Suddenly the sky is dark
And the rain begins to fall
All the messages I wrote to you
I erased then wrote them again
I'm just not strong enough
That's why I have to beg you
Could I stop myself falling for you?
Could I just talk to you?
Who do you love? If I could ask that
I wish I could be the answer
When did this feeling begin?
When will I stop loving you?
- I did it!
- Why do I love? Is there a reason?
I've no idea, it just turned out
that way. Love you
I'm in love
I'm over the moon
When you tell me you love me
I can't get enough of your love
If I tell you I love you
Will you run a mile?
How do you feel? I can't ask you
I'm sighing all the time and it hurts
I'm so sad I'm still in love with you
This is no way to be happy
How do I feel? Empty inside?
I guess it's okay
It's for the best Goodbye
Nanaka. I believe in you.
Hang in there.
Thank you.
I'm sorry but I'll do my best.
- I'll be at the festival.
- See you there! I will.
- Mai!
- Oh, this is a first.
She betrayed me,
so I'm your fan now.
Well, thank you.
Mai, you're the best singer
for sure.
- Thanks for your support.
- Yes, I'm with you.
Please come again.
Please line up if you have a ticket.
What the hell are you doing?
Time's up.
Everyone go to the back!
Everyone over here.
Follow me.
Mai!
- You okay?
- I'm okay.
Let go of me!
Please run!
Let's get out of here!
Coming through!
I'm closing it.
Are you okay?
I'm fine, see.
Thanks Mai.
For coming back for me.
It's all over the news.
Even on TV.
Our first time on TV.
Please, listen.
Okay, we are relieved you're all safe.
The car's coming.
We'll catch the last train as planned.
After what just happened?
For now we've decided
we should go ahead.
Sorry...
They wouldn't let me in.
Are you all okay?
Well...
Was that man one of the fans?
Leave that to the police.
Don't worry.
If the media asks you anything
just say you don't know.
Especially if they ask about fans.
You must never say anything bad.
Yes.
But it was Mr.Yama.
He came to all our gigs.
Really?
I don't know him.
Who is this Mr.Yama?
He's a fan of Nanaka's.
He came to all our gigs.
He bought dozens of CD's.
Just to spend a few minutes
talking to us.
We know him. All about him.
And all the fans.
We know their names, their hobbies,
their favorite colors,
and how to make them happy.
I can't stand this.
Mr.Yama... He was scary.
I thought he was going to kill me.
But...
It was the fans who protected me.
You look safe. I'm relieved.
Mai?
Hey...
You should go with them.
Go!
Just go!
- Drive!
- But...
Now!
Please.
Mai!
Why did you come?
I heard it on the news.
I rushed over.
Thank you.
Manager Saya
Shouldn't you answer?
No I won't.
I'm going to get in trouble anyway.
When I saw Mr.Yama
coming for me
all I could think about was you.
Me too...
I've missed you.
8 months later
Stand please.
Case number 371, 2024.
Suit for damages.
Plaintiff, Farrels Co. Ltd.
Director: Yoshida.
Defendants, Kei Mayama
and Mai Yamaoka.
We will now begin the sixth session.
Please call your witness.
I will show the witness
the contract Exhibit 2.
This is the contract that the
defendant signed.
You were present at the time?
That is correct.
Could you read it for us?
Yes.
Article 10: Termination of Contract.
The period is...
A little further on, please.
Okay.
If a performer has a relationship
with a fan
the company may cancel
the contract and claim damages.
Sexual relationships with
the opposite sex are forbidden.
This will result in the
termination of their contract.
Is this accurate?
Yes.
So, when the contract was signed,
was there any coercion,
or any inducements
offered to the defendant?
No.
The defendant carefully
checked the contract
and stamped it herself.
Did she have any questions or
concerns at that time?
No, she didn't.
What did you do before
you became a manager?
I was an idol in the same agency.
Did you sign a similar agreement?
Yes.
It had the same content.
It's a typical contract.
In your opinion,
what is the purpose of
the No Love Clause?
Being an idol is not a regular job.
Idols only exist because of the fans.
Sales from the events
are an important source of
income for the management.
Fans look forward to them.
To different degrees,
fans are in love with the idols.
The no love clause makes sense.
Exhibit 3.
Ms.Yamaoka's relationship
has damaged the group's image.
The client lost 8 million yen due to
canceled appearances
and the re-creation of merchandise.
Do you think this is
a reasonable amount?
Did you read the clause about
no relationships?
I didn't really understand it.
I only skimmed that part.
But you were aware of it?
I saw lots of idols on TV
when I was little.
So I sort of knew about it.
But...
I don't think I really had
any idea about relationships.
Tell us again how you felt
about the contract when you signed.
I...
I've loved idols since junior high school.
I took lots of auditions.
But I never passed.
In the second round
when I saw how confident
the others were, I lost heart.
I never passed.
I was about to give up,
when I auditioned for Happy Fanfare.
I was so happy to pass...
I just wanted to sign the contract
as soon as possible.
I'm so sad I'm still in love with you
This is no way to be happy
How do I feel? Empty inside?
I guess it's okay. It's for the best.
Love you
Hello everyone.
We are Happy Fanfare.
Our Japan tour has begun today!
You guys okay for money?
Are you eating alright?
- You're not her mum!
- Well, you know...
We're okay, but I'd be lying
if I said it was a walkover.
So it's tough?
It's tough.
- Lawyer's fees?
- For both of us.
It's not the same lawyer?
It's called "conflict of interest."
They're suing both of us for damages.
They calculate damages depending on
the degree of fault.
Fault?
I'm sorry but our love was "a fault."
That's ridiculous.
When is the verdict?
In two months,
after the cross examinations finish.
I hope the verdict will be fine.
Well, at least if they reduce
the damages from 8 million.
That's too much.
I think I'll quit the agency too.
Not now. That would mess
things up for the others.
If you need money just tell me.
Thanks.
But my dad said he'd help.
We decided not to take it.
- We didn't decide.
- Are we still on that?
- I know how you feel, but you're broke.
- I'm working part-time.
Don't fight.
I'm going to sing.
I'm working on it.
I really want to do my own stuff.
Will you listen?
Really?
Yes.
I really want to see if you like it.
I look up and see
A sky as blue as the deep blue sea
I'm all alone
Waiting for a special someone
Even my tears
Sparkle like the stars
In the night sky
Will I ever laugh again?
Far, far away
A light is beckoning me
But still...
I hear
The melody
With all my heart
I pray for this beautiful world
Let's sketch it together
Stop ego surfing!
Ego surfing.
I wasn't.
Yes, you were.
Yeah. I'm sorry. I was.
More nasty comments?
Less than before. Good and bad.
It's been almost a year.
The trial is boring.
Risa's song was good, wasn't it?
Yeah, it was good.
Risa said
she can't see me anymore.
The agency told her not to meet me.
When did she tell you?
When you were in the toilet.
Risa is so nice.
She came all the way to tell me.
I guess people will just
slowly forget about me.
You still have fans.
I've lost a lot of followers.
You're still popular.
I'm happy with my ten fans!
You haven't been gigging
on the street.
I'm getting other gigs.
Weddings?
Weddings are good.
It's regular and I get tips.
Everyone's in a good mood.
They'll laugh at anything.
But can you do what you like?
What do you mean?
I want you to be free.
- Going online?
- Yeah, you can go to sleep.
I'll wait. I have things to do.
I like to watch you sleeping.
You're so creepy!
Should I be in shot?
Stop it!
I'm starting.
Good evening everyone.
Good evening.
Can you see me?
Is the camera on?
Good evening.
Yey! Thank you!
This is my fifth live broadcast.
I'm getting used to it.
Can you hear me?
Yes, we can see you.
Thank you so much.
Great. Thanks a million.
Well, everyone...
I can't wait to see you all again.
Thanks for the love.
I love you all too.
Watch out!
Can you make it?
Did you know that Ms.Yamaoka was
an idol in Tokyo?
Did your friends tell you?
I had no idea.
So when you met her again,
you weren't a fan?
No.
You know the plaintiff has the right
to terminate if an idol dates a fan.
The defendant was not a fan,
so no breach of contract.
Who initiated the relationship?
Wasn't it Ms.Yamaoka?
I don't remember.
Did Ms.Yamaoka inform you
that she had signed a contract,
with the "no love" clause?
I had no idea...
That's not true.
My client is not bound by any contract.
He is the victim here.
But I did hear there was
an unspoken rule.
Let me ask you again.
Had you seen the contract?
No.
That's all.
Do you admit you had a relationship?
Yes.
When did this begin?
Begin?
I mean when did you get involved?
When you met again?
Who told the other one first?
We didn't have to do that.
I see.
So, you didn't say it in words.
But when did your sexual
relationship begin?
- That's not your business!
- Silence in court.
I object.
That's inappropriate.
The contract prohibits sexual relationships,
so it's a relevant question.
Objection over-ruled.
Please answer.
I don't want to say.
You're not denying you were intimate.
Final question.
Dating, love,
a sexual relationship...
Whatever it is, didn't your
thoughtless actions constitute
a betrayal of your fans and
the group?
I didn't think about it at the time.
You knew that idols should be pure
and that this was your job, right?
You acted the part of
an innocent girl around the fans, right?
How do you feel about your fans now?
I feel bad.
But you couldn't stop
seeing him, right?
No.
Why?
You felt guilty, didn't you?
I didn't want to lie
to myself anymore.
Hi there.
You're home.
I didn't see your van.
I got hungry.
How about you?
No, not yet.
What's this?
All this stuff.
Sorry, I haven't sorted it yet.
That's okay.
But where's your van?
I sold it.
You sold it. Why?
I thought it was
the right thing to do.
Because you needed the money?
No, I didn't.
Why then?
Well, I've got a home now,
and it costs to run the van.
- Why didn't you ask me?
- It's my van.
It's none of your business.
Do you mean that?
I'm just saying...
What?
I'm going to buy it back.
The van.
Hey, Mai!
Mai!
Mai! Come back!
I didn't tell you. They offered me
a job at the wedding hall.
3 months, renewable.
I thought it would be good to
change things up a bit.
Suit yourself!
Why are you so angry?
- You don't get it!
- Get what?
Forget it!
Give me a break and
stop being a brat!
I didn't want to sell it.
But I don't have a choice.
We're broke.
How are we going to pay?
We haven't lost yet.
But, I mean,
what will we do if we lose?
You decided not to
take my dad's money!
Who's the brat now?
You and your stupid ego!
We can pay him back later.
Together.
There's some progress.
Please contact us.
Your lawyer, Sasahara.
Sorry I'm late.
Good afternoon.
I am the defense council,
Sasahara.
Thank you for coming to us.
We have businesses, mainly in the
health food and mail-order sectors.
I am the CEO, Ito.
About your employer, Farrels...
Did you know that
we now own the agency?
Yes, I heard about it.
We want get into entertainment
without any controversy.
As a result of our internal discussions
about how to resolve the ongoing
court case,
we want to settle and that's why
we asked you here today.
These are the terms...
First, we would like you to
submit a written apology,
a formality to set an example
to the other talent.
A confidentiality agreement
stating that you will not
discuss this with anyone.
We will withdraw the claim
for damages in full,
taking into account
your future prospects.
For now, we'll take this away.
We'll get back to you.
Goodbye.
Miss Mai...
My nephew is in junior high school,
and he's a big fan.
Thank you.
Can we take a photo together?
I want to show it to my nephew.
Sure.
- Shall I hold your bag?
- Shall I take the photo?
I'll take it.
Okay.
Cheese.
One more.
Well, that's it then.
It's useless to go on.
We would just keep on arguing.
We need to get on with our lives.
You mean you want to quit?
And you Mai?
Do you still want to fight?
I want to accept.
Our future together is much more
important than this trial.
What are you fighting for, Mai?
Mai. Over here!
- This place is so far.
- I know.
- You commute from here every day?
- I got used to it.
Okay.
Hello there.
Thanks for coming to see Nanaka.
Did you recover?
I was worried.
Mother, mind your own business.
She's my only child
so I spoil her too much.
Thanks for the sweets, mum. Bye!
Stay as long as you like. Relax.
Have some.
I heard you'd been a bit sick.
I'm fine.
How are you though?
The girls are all dying to see you.
Happy Fanfare's new song's gone viral.
They say we're about to break big.
We're working so hard every day.
Nanaka, you know...
What?
Tell me.
You're making me nervous.
Do you still love Yuya?
Of course not.
We split up.
I'm sorry.
Why are you asking me then?
I feel bad about what happened.
I wasn't able to help you
guys stay together.
Why now? I wasn't thinking clearly
at the time. I was wrong.
No you weren't.
That's enough.
The agency is offering to settle.
I want to make it a condition that
they drop the no love clause.
Stop it!
You know it's not about the contract.
It's all about what the fans
want in the end.
You're right.
The group is fantastic now.
Only serious girls remain.
I hated to do my make-up,
but now I'm good.
The make-up artist fixes me up
before every gig.
It's like we're stars at last.
You must regret it though, Mai.
You can't go back.
You're kidding yourself
you made the right choice.
That's not true.
Yes, it is.
We were together every day.
I can tell.
I'm not like you Mai.
I'm an idol.
I know how you feel, but
please don't use me.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have said that.
What if we don't settle?
What if we go all the way?
What do you mean "all the way"?
If we lose, we take it to the
Supreme Court.
Well...
Of course, that's up to you both.
If you decide to do that
it will be difficult for me to
continue to defend you.
I think it will be difficult to win.
But we can introduce you to
another lawyer.
Yes.
I'll let you know, but
I believe that Mr.Mayama is willing
to settle.
I see.
It's the right choice.
You're both young,
so you can move on with your lives.
- Can we come in?
- I'm sorry.
Are you Mai from Happy Fanfare?
I'm a huge fan.
No, I'm not her I'm afraid.
You're her spitting image.
And you dance just like her. So cool.
You saw me?
I'm happy to hear that.
Do you like Happy Fanfare?
I'm going to audition soon.
Um, can you watch me?
I'll keep you to myself
Just for a second
Don't look away please
You're my only number one
Why are you waiting?
It's a one second love story
It's so simple this love
In one instant
You looked like you were having fun.
Yeah, it was fun.
And you've improved.
- Really?
- I thought so.
- Compared to those kids?
- That's not what I meant.
So, you're a fan now?
Big fan.
Hey...
Show me something.
Didn't you come together?
Well... no...
It came as a surprise.
What do you mean?
Haven't you heard?
No.
Excuse me.
This is Ms.Sugimura,
my new lawyer.
Nice to meet you.
Where's Mr.Sasahara?
I replaced him.
Why?
Thank you all for your hard work.
Now, I would like to begin by confirming
the settlement terms.
Can we proceed?
Go ahead.
After carefully examining the terms,
we have decided not to settle.
What's going on?
I'm sorry.
But, if we keep fighting, it's...
I'm really sorry, but I had to do this.
Is that your decision, Ms.Yamaoka?
You don't accept the settlement?
Mai...
Ms.Yamaoka?
That is correct. I won't settle.
And Mr.Mayama?
I...
will settle.
One final thing.
Go ahead.
Mai Yamaoka will file a suit
against the plaintiff.
She will sue for mental damages
caused by an unjust contract
that we regard as unconstitutional
and which breaches
her basic human rights.
We request testimony
from the agency.
How's it going lately?
Okay, I guess.
I loved your new song.
Thanks.
I never thought you'd write
a song for the group.
I feel bad for you Mai,
but I really want the girls to succeed.
Yeah.
Risa...
What?
Thank you for coming to the trial.
Sorry...
Why?
- It was like watching a play.
- What do you mean? I was so nervous.
- At the verdict you were so nervous.
- You cried!
Of course I cried.
It took a whole year.
You really fought for it.
Keep the praise coming.
Nanaka's a star now.
Of course.
She's so cute.
Yes.
Put your song on.
Okay.
Far Away Light.
Happy Fanfare.
I look up and see
A sky as blue as the deep blue sea
I'm all alone
Waiting for a special someone
Even my tears
Sparkle like the stars
What will you do?
I've no idea.
What about work?
I was asked to teach dance class.
That's great.
Yeah, but it's for kids.
But it's from spring.
I'm free now.
Time to find a boyfriend.
No. I'm through with relationships
for now.
When I'm old can I live with you?
Nice idea, but I've got someone.
What? No way!
Why didn't you tell me?
You met my partner
when we were in the group.
Who is it?
At the Zoo, and at Karaoke.
We're living together.
It only says you can't date
someone of the opposite sex.
Unbelievable. Beat that.
Here?
Yes.
It's beautiful.
Yeah.
I want Nanaka to see this.
Yeah. Me too.
Let's come here with her some day.
Yeah.
Let's go home.
It's cold.
Breakfast?
Something hot.
Let's get going.